J "渐黑J "
J“ fade into black j“
J "街道变得生机勃勃"
j“ the streets come alive j“
那个大城市的怪物
j“ that big city monster j“
刚睁开眼睛
j“ just opened his eyes j“
J "努力，肌肉，J "
j“ the hustle, the muscle j”
铬和钢
J“ the chrome and the steel j“
我得到了我想要的，宝贝
j“ got what I want, baby j'
"我们做个交易吧"
j“ let's make that deal j“
砰砰，把他们打死
j“ bang bang, shoot 'em up j“
J "谈论犯罪，J J "有人刚买了它在霓虹灯黏液里，J "
j“ talkin' 'bout crime j j“ somebody just bought it in the neon slime j“
每个人都淹没在霓虹灯下
j“ everybody's drownin' in the neon slime j'
你看，我是幸存者，我知道那是什么感觉
j“ you see I'm the survivor j j“ and I know how it feels j“
成为夜晚时光的一部分，一切都是真实的，
j“ to be part of the night time j j“ where everything is real j'
音乐，暴力
j“ the music, the violence j'
j性，甜蜜的气味j j我是一个冰冷的信徒j j在地狱的快乐j j砰砰，射他们j j感觉很好j j在河中受洗j j霓虹黏液j
j the sex, the sweet smell j j I'm a stone-cold believer j j in the pleasures of hell j j bang bang, shoot 'em up j j feelin' just fine j j been baptized in the river j j of the neon slime j
J是的，这是真的J J这是你特别的梦想J J比生活更大J J这会让你想要尖叫J J这是最新的愤怒J J最新的热门J J现在它来了J
j yes, it's real j j it's your special dream j j larger than life j j it's gonna make you wanna scream j j it's the latest rage j j and the latest hit j j now here it comes j
j它会给你带来快乐j j也会给你带来一些痛苦j j但我向你保证j j你将不再是以前的j j来品尝我的蜂蜜，品尝我的酒j j来触摸我的灵魂j
j it'll bring you pleasure j j and bring you some pain j j but I promise you this j j you'll never be the same j j come taste my honey and taste my wine j J come touch my soul j
在队伍的最后砰砰砰，枪崩他们谈论犯罪J J每个人都在霓虹黏液中游泳J J街道上到处都是霓虹黏液
j at the end of the line j j bang bang, shoot 'em up j j talkin' 'bout crime j j everybody's swimmin' in the neon slime j j the streets are flowin' with neon slime j
j每个人，每个人j j每个人都走在霓虹灯上j j那个霓虹灯，j j那个霓虹灯，j j是的，是的j -下一班去圣地亚哥的巴士几点开?
j everybody, everybody, everybody j j everybody walkin' on neon slime j j that neon slime j j the neon j j the neon slime j j yeah, yeah j - what time is the next bus to San Diego?
谢谢你！
Thank you.
好吧,宝贝。
Okay, sweetheart.
该穿衣服了，好吗，因为妈妈很着急。
Time to get dressed, okay, 'cause mommy's in a big hurry.
好姑娘。
Good girl.
你要带着你所有的毛绒玩具下去见奶奶吗?
You're gonna take all your stuffed animals to go down and see grandma?
嗯?
Hmm?
啊哈。
Uh-huh.
-让我看看。
- Let me see.
我爱你，小鸭子，我爱你。
I love you, punky duck, I love you.
我也爱你，妈妈。
I love you too, mommy.
-好了，现在，你把行李收拾好，好吗?妈妈去穿衣服，好吗?
- Okay, now, you finish packing, okay, and mommy's gonna go get dressed, all right.
——好女孩。
- Good girl.
天啊，小布，我还以为你来不了了。
Jesus, b, I didn't think you were gonna make it.
-碧翠丝总是做的。
- Beatrice always makes it.
我得装出一副旅行的样子。
Just had to put on my traveling face.
这通知也太仓促了吧。
Well, that was a mighty short notice.
-巴士30分钟后出发。
- Well, the bus leaves in 30 minutes.
所以呢?
So?
丽莎?
Lisa?
B在这里。
B is here.
嗨,b。
Hi, b.
你错过了一班车，她肯定能赶上另一班车。
- You miss one bus she sure can catch another.
-我没有时间浪费在等公共汽车上。
- I don't have time to waste waiting for a bus.
不是今晚,b。
Not tonight, b.
-你不接吗?
- Aren't you gonna answer?
这是姜。
It's ginger.
-等等，小姜。
- Hold on, ginger.
B，带她上出租车。
B, take her on out to the cab.
我马上就出来。
I'll be out in a couple of seconds.
嘿，怎么了?
Ging, what is it?
-我分了ramrod。
- I split on ramrod.
-我的小公主怎么样了?
- How's my little Princess?
-拜托，b，我让你永远不要这么叫她。
- Please, b, I asked you never to call her that.
-哦，对不起。
- Oh, I'm sorry.
-金吉，怎么了?
- Ginger, what's wrong?
-我抛弃了他。
- I ran out on him.
我受不了了。
I couldn't take it.
他把我打得半死。
He beat the shit out of me.
我受不了了。
I can't handle it anymore.
-金吉，你在哪?
- Ginger, where are you?
-我在好莱坞日落旅馆。
- I'm at the Hollywood sunset motel.
-天啊，他肯定会找到你的
- Oh, Jesus, he'll find you there for sure.
-我瞒着他
- I held out on him.
500美元。
-金吉，看在上帝的份上，听我说。
- Ginger, for Christ's sakes, listen to me.
马上把门栓上。
Bolt the door, right now.
别让任何人进来，好吗。
Don't let anybody in, okay.
我九点要去见沃尔什然后我就过去，好吗?
I gotta go see Walsh at nine and then I'll be over afterwards, okay?
——承诺?
- Promise?
-是的，我保证，好吗?
- Yes, I promise, okay?
我们现在在七号门装货。
We're now loading at door number seven.
接待前往奥克兰和旧金山的乘客。
Receiving passengers for Oakland and San Francisco.
开往圣地亚哥的特快列车现在最后一次呼叫，从13号门出发。
Final call for express car now leaving door 13 for San Diego.
当地服务现在接受乘客，5号门前往长滩，圣克莱门特，拉霍亚和圣地亚哥。
Local services now receiving passengers, door five for long beach, San clemente, la jolla and San Diego.
今晚谁会想念她的妈妈?
Who's gonna miss her mommy tonight?
-我要你跟我来，妈妈。
- I want you to come with me, mommy.
-我也是，亲爱的。
- I do too, sweetheart.
我爱你。
I love you.
再见,公主。
Bye, Princess.
替我照顾好她，b。
Take care of her for me, b.
再见,再见。
Bye, bye.
-我爱你。
- I love you.
的关注。
Attention.
请停在巴士区黄色轻型巡洋舰的车主把车开走好吗?
Will the owner of the yellow corvette parked in the bus area please move your car?
前往西雅图和温哥华的旅客请在九号门登机。
Now boarding passengers at door number nine for Seattle and Vancouver.
哦,对不起。
Oh, excuse me.
一些女孩。
- Some girls.
-喂，妈妈，该下来了
- Say, mama, it's time to get down.
-别跟我说话，荡妇，除非你有钱。
- Don't even talk to me, jive ass, unless you've got some money.
去丹佛的最后一次电话是10号门。
Final call at door number 10 for Denver.
——嘿,甜心。
- Hey, sweetheart.
我们聚一聚怎么样?
How about us getting together?
亲爱的,叫公主。
Name's Princess, honey.
你有什么想法?
What have you got in mind?
-火辣的动作，宝贝。
- Some hot action, baby.
我刚发工资。
I just got paid.
我加载。
I'm loaded.
——加载,嗯?
- Loaded, huh?
那么，你想要真正的激情时刻吗?
Well, then, you want a real hot time?
-这就是我来的原因。
- That's why I'm here for.
-你为什么不去找个漂亮的女警察?
- Why don't you just go find yourself a nice little lady cop?
-来吧，亲爱的。
- Come on, sweetie.
你觉得我像警察吗?
Do I look like a cop to you?
泰迪熊有棉球吗?
- Does the Teddy bear have cotton balls?
迷路了,是吗?
Get lost, huh?
但作为警察，你挺可爱的。
But you're pretty cute for a cop.
-这是6号，维克多6号。
- This is six Victor six.
我现在要离开好莱坞车站。
I'm leaving the Hollywood bus station now.
——嘿,亲爱的。
- Hey, honey.
你只是出去兜风?
You're just out cruising?
50美元能给我带来什么?
Um, what will $50 get me?
-很高兴见到你。
- Well, a whole lot of pleasure.
好吧，一半一半，直，头。
Well, half-and-half, straight, head.
-你洗过金色淋浴吗?
- Have you ever golden showered?
我是说这不会疼什么的。
I mean it doesn't hurt or anything.
-抱歉，亲爱的，我去了趟洗手间。
- Sorry, lover, I just went to the restroom.
-我有六块啤酒和100美元。
- I have a six pack and $100.
-你还和自来水公主约会了。
- You also got yourself a date with Princess running water.
明天,9个?
Tomorrow, nine?
你说对了，ramrod。
You got it, ramrod.
哦，我爱你。
Oh, I love you.
好吧，你不能回头看J你不能一直说J当没有什么可说的J J，是他，J
J well you can't look behind j j you can't just keep on talkin' j j when there's nothing left to say j j and it's him j
混蛋，我说的是50。
Motherfucker, I said 50.
50？
50 !
-是谁?
- Who is it?
-全能的上帝，就是他。
- It's god almighty, that's who it is.
来吧,宝贝。
Come on, baby.
打开门。
Open up the door.
-我不会让你进来的，你个混蛋。
- I ain't letting you in, you prick.
-金吉，别这么跟我说话。
- Ginger, don't talk to me that way.
-你又要打我?
- You're gonna hit me again?
-你知道吗，你是我心中的头等大事。
- Well, you know, you're the number one thing in my heart.
来吧,宝贝。
Come on, baby.
开门。
Open up the door.
我一个人在这里。
I'm out here all alone.
我不会让你把我打趴下的。
I ain't letting you beat my ass to the floor.
-亲爱的，我想做的就是爱你。
- Honey, all I wanna do, is just love you.
-你把我伤得很重。
- You hurt me bad, ramrod.
-我知道我做了。
- I know I did.
但那是因为我以为你对我有所隐瞒。
But that's 'cause I thought you was holding out on me.
我早该知道的。
I should have known better.
我早该知道你不会做那样的事。
I should have known you wouldn't do a thing like that.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
宝贝,我很抱歉。
Baby, I'm sorry.
我永远不会打你的。
I ain't never gonna hit you.
我只想给你你想要的那种爱。
All I wanna do is give you the kind of love you want.
你所需要的东西。
What you need.
开门，小姜。
Open the door, ginger.
-你发誓不会再打我了?
- You swear you ain't gonna hit me again?
——这是正确的。
- That's right.
金吉，开门。
Ginger, open the door.
来吧。
Come on.
开门。
Open the door.
我真不敢相信你有多蠢。
I cannot believe how stupid you are.
忘恩负义的臭婊子。
Ungrateful fucking bitch.
我照顾过你，不是吗?
I took care of you, didn't I?
不是吗?
Didn't I?
回答我。
Answer me.
我不是照顾过你吗?
Didn't I take care of you, huh?
是我在车站发现你快饿死的
I'm the one who found you at the bus station half starving to death.
是我教你把头发扎起来，把妆化得恰到好处，这样你就可以随心所欲地和约翰约会了。
I'm the one who taught you to put your hair up, put your makeup on just right, So you could have any John you want.
你怎么还我的?
How did you pay me back, huh?
你是怎么还我的，小姜?
How did you pay me back, ginger?
不要动!
Don't move!
不要动。
Don't move.
你怎么还我的?
How did you pay me back, huh?
你没有瞒着我。
You don't hold out on me.
-我爱你，拉姆罗德。
- I love you, ramrod.
——什么?
- What?
你爱我吗?
You love me?
你爱我。
You love me.
看，我也爱你，小姜。
See, I love you, too, ginger.
我真的。
I really do.
但你知道吗，小姜，坊间传言说你想把我当逃犯。
But you know what, ginger, the street talk has it that you're thinking about turning outlaw on me.
现在假设你告诉我这不是真的。
Now suppose you tell me that's not true, all right.
我发誓我不会离开你的，拉姆。
I swear I won't leave you, ram.
——你发誓。
- You swear.
你对天发誓?
You swear to god, hmm?
哦,是的。
Oh, yeah.
你说的没错。
You bet your sweet ass.
你不能离开我。
You ain't leaving me.
我不让你走，你就别走。
You don't leave until I say so.
我是说，你知道我该怎么做。
I mean, you know what I got to do.
天啊，我得帮你重新振作起来。
God, I gotta help you get your act back together.
我该怎么办?
What am I supposed to do?
你看，金格小姐，
You see, miss ginger,
你要做的是，你要知道没有人会抛弃我。
what you've got to do, is you got to learn that nobody ever walks out on me.
你理解我吗?
You understand me?
不会的，他们不会抛弃我的。
Nevefl they never walk out on me.
你和我，
And you and me,
你和我，宝贝，我们会继续互相帮助，
you and me, baby, we're gonna go on helping each other,
直到我说我们不再需要互相帮助。
till I say we don't need to help each other no more.
当你吸取教训后，生姜
When you've learned that lesson, ginger,
你会感觉很好。
you're gonna feel so good.
我是说，你会为自己感到高兴的。
I mean, you'll feel happy about yourself.
你懂我的意思吧?
You know what I mean, hmm?
现在我跟你说话的时候你看着我。
Now you look at me when I'm talking to you.
你知道现在几点了吗?
Do you know what time it is?
该上学了。
It's school time.
在很长一段时间内你都不能把我的赚钱机器给别人。
You ain't gonna be able to give my money maker away for quite a while.
第一课，小姜。
Lesson number one, ginger.
6号亚伯7号，东经546，北海沃德327。
Six Abel seven, at 546 e, 327 north hayward.
你们都安全了，6号，维克多10号。
You're all clear six Victor 10.
没有消息。
No messages.
——啊,
- Ah,
好的,警官。
okay, sergeant.
我再讲一遍。
Let me run through this again.
我同意，这事很棘手，对吧?
Now, agreed, it's up the ass, right?
在世界各地，这就是，操和吸。
Around the world, that's, fuck and suck.
-不不不
- No, no, no.
爱德华兹,这是不明确的。
Edwards, that's half-and-half.
-没错，伙计，没错。
- Right, man, right.
我得到了它。
I got it.
黄金淋浴是一个喜欢被撒尿的怪胎。
A golden shower is a freak who likes to get pissed on.
对吧?
Right?
——嗯。
- Mmm-hmm.
哇,人。
Whoo, man.
这是生病。
That is sick.
-是啊，我们又不是在这里写交通罚单。
- Yeah, well, we ain't out here writing traffic citations.
爱德华兹，我有几句忠告，你最好习惯。
And Edwards, few words of advice, you better get used to it.
你花钱请人做的吗?
Did you pay to have that done?
——什么?
- What?
——你的……——我的小辫吗?-是的。
- Your... - My cornrows? - Yeah.
-当然了，伙计。
- Of course, man.
多少钱?
How much?
多少钱,是吧?
How much, huh?
-怎么了，中士?
- What's the matter, sergeant?
你不喜欢我的玉米辫?
You don't like my cornrows?
-我喜欢你的玉米辫
- Yeah, I like your cornrows.
等一等。
Hold on.
我们有客人来了。
We got ourselves a customer here now.
好的,我的朋友。
Okay, my friend.
我们要给你开个婚。
We're gonna pop your cherry.
你出去把那个小妓女带过来。
You go out and bring that little hooker over here.
-警官，我一直带着牙买加口音工作。
- Sergeant, I've been working with this Jamaican accent.
我现在可以用吗?
Can I use it now?
用你的牙买加口音。
Yeah, use your Jamaican accent.
-好吧，警官。
- All right, sergeant, man.
——嗨,官。
- Hi, officer.
我能为您做些什么?
What can I do for you?
嘿,男人。
- Hey, man.
你以为我是警察?
You think I'm a cop?
光是说这个词就让我紧张。
Just saying the word make me nervous.
——坚持。
- Hold on.
你想参加派对吗?
You want to party?
-我想也许你想狂欢一下，是吧?
- Eh, I think maybe you want to party, huh?
尤其是和我这样的帅哥在一起。
Especially with a pretty boy like me.
你喜欢我的头发吗?
You like my hair?
-我喜欢你的微笑。
- I like your smile.
你打算花多少钱买，宝贝?
So how much you wanna spend for it, baby?
- 35美元?
- $35?
-那会让你头脑清醒的。
- That'll get you some real good head.
你觉得怎么样?
How about that?
——这很好。
- That's fine.
嗨,蓝筹股。
Hi, blue chip.
——好吧,好。
- Well, well.
这不是小崽子先生吗。
If it isn't Mr. Pussycuffs.
——这就是我。
- That's me.
-听着，伙计，你别想抓我。
- Listen, man, you ain't gonna hang no snatch and grab on me.
我没有给他报价。
I didn't give him an offer.
-你得原谅他，因为他是新来的。
- Well, you gotta forgive the boy because he's new.
他不知道你在说吸蛋。
He didn't know that you were talking about sucking eggs.
——大便。
- Shit.
-快点，快点。
- Come on, move it.
-老兄，我再说一遍。
- Man, I'm gonna tell you again, man.
我是个皮条客。
I am a pimp.
你明白我的意思吗，伙计?
You understand what I'm saying, man?
问问我那位女士就知道了。
Just ask my lady there, man.
她会告诉你。
She'll tell you.
我也不是什么摇头晃脑的毒贩。
I ain't no god damn, jive ass dope dealer either.
我是个皮条客。
I am a pimp.
-我对天发誓，警官。
- I swear to god, officer.
我不是想摸那个男人。
I was not trying to grope that man.
我是说，这是个无心之过。
I mean, it was an honest mistake.
我只是想把他裤子上的灰掸掉。
I was merely trying to dust the ashes off his pants.
-格雷戈里，格雷戈里，你上周就是这么说的，亲爱的。
- Gregory, Gregory, that's what you said last week, sweetie.
——哦,大便。
- Oh, shit.
一个女孩这么努力也不能怪她。
Well, can't blame a girl for trying.
-嘿，卢，过来，把这个废物从我面前拿开，好吗?
- Hey, Lou, come over here and get this bum out of my face, huh?
-嘿，这两个婊子是谁的?
- Hey, who belongs to these two whores?
-我们不是妓女，魁梧的警察先生。
- We ain't no whores, Mr. Hunky policeman.
我们是妓女。
We're prostitutes.
-有区别吗?
- There's a difference?
-妓女送人。
- Whores give it away.
愚蠢的。
Stupid.
-不是应该有人带这孩子去少管所吗?
- Hey, wasn't somebody supposed to take this kid to juvenile?
-你他妈凭什么认为我想进少管所。
- What the fuck makes you think I wanna go to juvenile.
-你觉得自己很坚强，是吗，孩子?
- You think you're tough, don't you, kid?
我们来看看你有多坚强。
We'll see how tough you are.
——不!
- No!
有人偷了我的回形针。
Somebody stole my goddamn paper clips.
谁他妈拿了我的回形针?
Who in the fuck took my paper clips?
每次你带东西来这破地方，你都找不到东西。
Every time you bring something to this fucking slime pit, you can't find shit.
现在有人偷了我的回形针。
Now somebody stole my goddamn paper clips.
那些是我的回形针。
Those were my paper clips.
我的纸夹。
My paper clips.
也许是时候让梅斯去吃草了?
- Maybe it's time for mace to be put out to pasture?
-也许是时候把我们都赶走了。
- Maybe it's time for all of us to be put out to pasture.
嘿，能给我女朋友拿点纸吗?
Hey, may I have some paper for my girlfriend here?
——嘿,沃尔什?
- Hey, Walsh?
沃尔什，他们要你马上去湾郡。
Walsh, they want you down at county bay immediately.
他们说这很重要。
They said it was important.
-门德斯，帮爱德华兹处理他的女朋友。
- Hey, Mendez, process Edwards' girlfriend for him.
六个维克多10。
Six Victor 10.
关于你们在郡医院的会面。
Regarding your meet at county med.
配上姜味格雷迪。
It's with a ginger Grady.
有人建议我们把它改成代号2半。
We've been advised to make that a code two and a half.
- 6号维克多10号。
- Six Victor 10.
罗杰中央。
Roger central.
你怎么知道她是妓女?
How do you know she was a hooker?
——阴道切除。
- Vaginal mutilation.
这在妓女中并不罕见。
It's not uncommon with prostitutes.
-拉皮条的棍子?
- A pimp stick?
-毫无疑问。
- No question about it.
她是怎么来的?
How the hell did she get here?
她乘出租车来的。
She arrived in a taxi.
-沃尔什
- Walsh,
是你吗?
is that you?
——是的,姜。
- Yeah, ginger.
那就是我。
That's me.
你现在告诉我真相。
You tell me the truth now.
是拉姆罗德干的。
Ramrod did this to you.
是ramrod，对吧?
It was ramrod wasn't it?
嗯?
Huh?
——没有。
- No.
他爱我。
He loves me.
-那个吸毒的疯子谁都不爱。
- That stoned psycho doesn't love anybody.
如果你做不到呢?
What if you don't make it, huh?
-我会成功的。
- I'm gonna make it.
我不想死。
I don't wanna die.
——放松
- Easy, easy.
即使这是我做的最后一件事，我也要抓住那个混蛋。
I'm gonna get that son of a bitch if it's the last thing I ever do.
-在你的临终遗言上
- Not on that death bed statement you won't.
门德斯打来电话，他说公主在车站等你。
Mendez called, he said Princess is waiting for you down at the station.
-你把她带来了。
- You have her brought here.
蓝色警报，四楼，一号床。
Code blue, fourth floor, bed one.
员工会议。
Staff meeting.
所有医生到11号病房报到。
All doctors report to room 11.
-这是什么?
- What is this?
开玩笑吗?
Some kind of a joke?
我可不想在你的僵尸旁边说话。
I'm not talking business near zombies of yours.
-你想谈笔交易吗?
- Do you wanna talk a deal, huh?
我们现在就在这里谈因为我没时间跟你胡闹，公主殿下。
We talk right now, right here because I don't have time to fuck around with you, Princess.
-好吧，这对任何人来说都是一个摆脱曲奇的好方法。
- Well, this is a hell of a way for anyone to get their cookies off.
-听着，你太不自量力了，亲爱的。
- Listen, you're over your head, sweetheart.
你的缉毒行动可以判3到10年。
That drug bust of yours is good for three to 10.
-拜托，沃尔什。
- Come on, Walsh.
别烦我了。
Get off my back.
你知道我不吸毒的，沃尔什。
You know I don't use dope, Walsh.
所以你为什么不放松点呢。
So why don't you just lighten up.
-你不用说服我，宝贝。
- You don't have to sell me, baby.
我知道你不吸毒。
I know you don't use dope.
我知道它。
I know it.
但你看，法官，他不知道。
But you see, the judge, he doesn't know.
你想让我放松点吗?
You want me to lighten up?
好吧，这个怎么样?
Okay, how is this?
你上庭就输了。
You go to trial and you lose.
你会输的。
And you will lose.
那个法官只要看一眼你的犯罪记录就会把你甩得屁滚尿流。
That judge is gonna take one look at your rap sheet and he's gonna dump all over you.
还有你的女儿，你的小女儿。
And your daughter, your little daughter.
她叫什么名字?
What's her name?
那个漂亮的小女孩，金发小女孩。
What, that beautiful little girl, little blonde girl.
她叫什么名字?
What's her name?
嗯?
Huh?
它是什么?
What is it?
丽莎,不是吗?
Lisa, isn't it?
嗯?
Huh?
——丽莎。
- Lisa.
- Lisa, right.
让我告诉你。
Let me tell you something.
在你重见天日之前，她就会出来耍花招了。
She will be out turning tricks before you see daylight again.
你有多想被打破?
How badly do you wanna break?
——好的,沃尔什。
- Okay, Walsh.
我们别扯这些破事了，好吗?
Let's get past the shit, all right?
告诉我你在想什么。
Just tell me what you got on your mind.
-我要你去经营一个皮条客
- I want you to operate a pimp
我叫拉姆罗德。
by the name of ramrod.
-把沙子塞到屁眼里去，沃尔什。
- Go put sand up your ass, Walsh.
你知道那个神经病喜欢什么吗?
Do you know what that psycho son of a bitch gets off on?
他以切割女孩为乐。
He gets off on cutting up girls.
-有了你的帮助，我们就能把他抓起来。
- And with your help we could put him away.
-你胆子真大，沃尔什
- You got big balls, Walsh.
你知道我有个孩子。
You know I got a kid.
如果那条蛇把我绑在床上，她会怎么做?
What's she gonna do if that snake trusses me up to some bed?
-你没得选。
- You don't have any choice.
不是这个就是监狱。
It's either this or the slammer.
就我个人而言，女士，我觉得你没时间了。
And personally, lady, I don't think you can handle the time.
-我可以活下去的，伙计。
- Well, I could stay alive, man.
他入狱24小时后就会被释放。
你他妈又不是在开监狱。
That's no fucking jail you're operating there.
这是一家有旋转门的酒店。
It's a hotel with a revolving door.
-我不需要什么婊子来告诉我系统出了什么问题。
- I don't need some fucking bimbo telling me what's wrong with the system.
你知道你的系统能做什么吗，亲爱的?
You know what you can do with your system, honey?
-姜·格雷迪呢?
- What about ginger Grady?
她是你的朋友，对吧?
She's a friend of yours, isn't she?
嗯?
Huh?
-你知道我们关系很好
- You know we're tight.
你因为我带了她的东西而逮捕了我。
You got a dope bust on me for carrying her shit.
-如果她跟你说话，你会这么做吗?
- Well, would you do it if she talked to you?
嗯?
Huh?
-你做了什么，也抓了她吗?
- What did you do, bust her too?
-不，不完全是，但我觉得她想和你谈谈。
- No, not exactly, but I think she wants to talk to you.
看看她，公主。
Look at her, Princess.
听她的。
Listen to her.
听她真正的好。
Listen to her real good.
是拉姆罗德干的。
Ramrod did that to her.
他把她打得半死。
He beat the shit out of her.
他用拉皮条的棍子打了她。
And he used a pimp stick on her.
-你面对他，胆小鬼。
- You face him, fucking coward.
-你怎么了?
- What's the matter with you?
你不关心吗?
Don't you care?
你整天坐着说"他打败我了，打败我了。”
All you is sit around all day saying, "he beat me, beat me.“
如果你不让我们帮你，我们要怎么保护你?
how are we supposed to protect if you don't let us help you?
看，看她。
Look, look at her.
看看她，公主。
Look at her, Princess.
她是你的朋友。
She's your friend.
-哦,上帝。
- Oh, god.
我从没说过我很坚强
J I never said that I was strong j
但你的爱对我的灵魂是最好的
j but your love is the best thing for this soul j
J你可以悲伤J J不要为我而去J J不大可能J J社会J耶，耶，耶
j and you can be sad j j don't go for me j j improbable j j society j j yeah, yeah, yeah j
-嘿，嘿，嘿。
- hey, hey, hey.
看看我们得到了什么。
Look at what we got here.
嗯嗯。
Mmm-mmm.
你的约会对象在哪里?
Where's your date at?
你知道吗，如果美丽是一分钟，妈妈，你就是一小时。
Do you know that if beauty was a minute, mama, you'd be an hour.
婊子，你没听见我在跟你说话吗?
Hey, bitch, don't you hear me talking to you, huh?
我在跟你说话。
I'm talking to you.
你知道我是谁吗?
I mean, you know who I am?
也许你不知道我是谁。
Maybe you don't know who I am.
也许我该去找你，这样你就知道我是谁了。
Maybe I should run it down to you so you know who I am.
宝贝，我是最棒的…——滚蛋。
Baby, I'm the best... - Fuck off.
-伙计，你是个冷酷的妈妈。
- Man, you're a cold mama.
你的问题是什么?
What's your problem?
谁是婊子?
Who's the bitch?
-怎么了，中士?
- What's the matter, sergeant?
——她的紧张。
- She's nervous.
-她很害怕，伙计。
- She's scared, man.
-如果他把她当成圈套，她就死定了。
- If he makes her as a setup, she's dead.
-你好，美女。
- Hello there, beautiful lady.
我请你喝一杯怎么样?
What do you say I buy you a drink?
-我可以自己买，牛仔。
- I can buy my own, cowboy.
-来吧。
- Now, come on.
不要UN-neighborly。
Don't be UN-neighborly.
我只是想表示友好，你明白吗?
I'm just trying to be friendly, do you understand?
开始一段对话。
Strike up a little conversation.
-都是你说的，帅哥
- Well, you're doing all the talking, handsome man.
-现在，在我看来你在单飞。
- Now, it appears to me that you're flying solo.
而且在我看来，你需要的是一个好人，一个能照顾你的人，对吗?
And it also appears to me that what you need is a good man, just somebody to take care of you, am I right?
我说的对吗?
Am I right, hmm?
-你觉得你能给我我想要的吗?
- Do you think you can give me what I need, huh?
-我什么都不给。
- I don't give nothing.
但如果你选对了我，我就得看看你的资历，不是吗?
But then, if you're choosing me well, I just have to see your qualifications, wouldn't I?
嗯?
Huh?
-我从来没听过我的男人抱怨过。
- I ain't never heard no man of mine complain before.
-我可以当警察，不是吗?
- I could be a cop, couldn't I?
-我可能还是处女。
- And I could be a virgin.
-哦，我也希望。
- Ooh, I wish.
你很有风格，宝贝。
You've got style, baby.
但如果我要接受你的申请，你和我，我们应该去个真正安静的地方。
But if I'm gonna take your application, you and I, we should go some place else where it's a real quiet.
我们说话。
We talk.
你觉得呢?
What do you think?
-你有什么想法?
- What have you got in mind?
——回家。
- Home.
我有一间漂亮的小公寓可以照顾你。
See, I got this beautiful little apartment where I take care of you.
你明白吗?
Do you understand?
明白吗?
Understand?
你喜欢吗?
Do you like that shit?
你喜欢吗，贱人?
You like that shit, bitch?
我喜欢它。
I like it.
如此疯狂的事情。
Such a wild thing.
跟我来，好吗?
Come with me, all right?
来吧。
Come on.
来吧,现在。
Come on, now.
这样我就能走路了，我把它带进来了，我们都给了，和我的朋友们，找到它并不难
J so I can walk my feet j j I was bringing it in rightly j j we're giving it all j j with friends of mine j j isn't all that hard to find j
-我带你去前面，所有的。
- I'll show you the front, all of them.
-是啊，你好吗，美女?
- Yeah, how you doing, beautiful?
-这些人不是好人。
- These people are no good.
你要带这个女孩去哪里?
Where are you going with this girl?
别跟他走。
Don't go with him.
去死吧，好吗?
Going to hell, all right?
-去死吧。-你烂透了，烂透了。
- Going to hell. - You're rotten, rotten.
你……-你想烧吗?
You're... - You wanna burn, huh?
你想燃烧吗?
You wanna burn?
我是魔鬼，宝贝。
I'm the devil, baby.
疯子。
Maniac.
别跟他走。
Don't go with him.
这是六组维克多10，全部六组。
This is six Victor 10, all six Victor units.
嫌犯和友军正前往你所在的位置。
Suspect and friendly, are headed to your location.
交通很清淡，所以你最好就位，因为他们只有几秒钟的路程。
Traffic is light so you better be in position because they're only seconds away.
- 6号，维克多3号。
- Six Victor three.
亚伯的位置。
Abel in position.
- 6号，维克多3号。
- Six Victor three.
男孩的位置。
Boy in position.
所以他们叫你公主。
So they call you the Princess.
是的，我可以。
Yes, uh, that works for me.
他们在上来的路上。
They're on their way up.
- 6号维克多3号亚伯。
- Six Victor three Abel.
嫌犯和友军已经进入电梯。
Suspect and friendly have entered the elevator.
你活了多久了，公主?
So how long you've been in the life, Princess?
五年了，平安夜。
Five years, Christmas Eve.
不得不流浪街头谋生。
Had to hit the streets to make a living.
-那你为什么要与众不同呢?
- Well, why should you be different, huh?
我能请你喝一杯吗，亲爱的?
Can I buy you a drink now, honey?
-威士忌，如果你有的话。
- Scotch if you've got it.
-如果有威士忌的话。
- Scotch if I got.
我得到了它。
I got it.
你说呢?
What do you say?
我去弄点喝的，然后你给我看看你有什么?
I'll make a little drink and then you show me what you got?
脱掉裙子，是吗?
Off with the dress, huh?
-你怎么没有主母?
- How come you don't have no main lady?
-我怎么没有主母?
- How come I don't got no main lady?
因为她瞒着我我只好炒了那个懒婊子。
It's because she held out on me and I just had to fire the lazy bitch.
你明白我的意思吗?
You know what I mean?
如此疯狂的事情。
Such a wild thing.
我能帮你吗?
Can I help you?
就让我今晚继续喝酒吧
J just let me keeping drinking tonight j
来吧，留在我身边
j come along and stay by my side j
留下来陪我，看着我回家好吗，做个朋友，尽量不要问我问题让我今晚继续喝酒
j stay with me and see that I get home j j all right j j be a friend and try not j j to ask me questions j j just let me keep drinking tonight j
好吧，这不会让我感觉好一点你很漂亮。
j well, it won't make me feel j j any better j - you're pretty.
太漂亮了。
So pretty.
哦,我的。
Oh, my.
这样一个优秀的。
Such a thoroughbred.
你和我将进入preakness。
You and me are going to enter into the preakness.
拿三冠。
Take the triple crown.
把手给我。
Give me your hand.
告诉我,公主。
Show me, Princess.
不,不,不。
No, no, no.
为我演奏，宝贝。
Play for me, baby.
打给我。
Play for me.
哦,是的。
Oh, yes.
你闻起来像玫瑰。
You smell like a Rose.
就让我今晚继续喝酒吧
J just let me keep drinking tonight j
好吧，这不会让我感觉好一点
j well, it won't make me feel any better j
美丽。
Beautiful.
——好。
- Well.
你只要帮我耍几招，把钱给我，我就帮你搞定一切，亲爱的。
You just turn a few tricks for me and give me the money and I'll take care of everything you need, honey.
-我们知道了。
- We got it.
让我们打他。
Let's hit him.
加油！加油
Come on, come on.
我们在。
We're going in.
-我想我恋爱了。
- I think I'm in love.
是的,我喜欢。
Yes, I do.
-把手放在头上，先生。
- Hands on your head, mister.
你到底在干什么?
What the hell are you doing?
-把衣服穿上，女士。
- Put your clothes on, lady.
-马上给我看搜查令，小子。
- Let me see a warrant right now, boy.
——权证?
- Warrants?
我们不需要什么搜查令因为我们正用右手抓着，该死的小垃圾。
We don't need no stinking warrants because we're holding them in our right hands, fucking little trash.
-检查卧室。
- Check the bedroom.
把你的手放在头上。
Put your hands on your head.
-嘿，警察，来吧。
- Hey, cop, come on.
拍我。
Shoot me.
-可以安排。
- That can be arranged.
哦，我打赌会的。
Oh, I'll bet it can.
-来吧，带他走
- Come on, take him.
没人拿到那该死的少数派报告。
Nobody got the fucking minority report.
我不是看到你在盐沼里摘莴苣了吗。
Say, didn't I see you picking lettuce in salinas.
加油！加油
Come on, come on.
-你没事吧?
- Are you okay, huh?
-我会做到的。
- I'll make it.
——在这里。
- Here.
现在，我很怕痒。
Now, I'm very ticklish.
- - - - - -来吧。
- Come on.
-你要下去了，警察?
- You're getting off down there, cop, huh?
你可以下车了，混蛋。
You're getting off, motherfucker.
-看到了吗，混蛋?
- You see this, asshole?
他们把我们说的话都录下来了。
They've recorded everything we said.
你的屁股现在就在这盘带子上，大概有这么大。
Your ass is on this tape now and it's about this big.
你要为你对金吉做的事付出代价。
Well, you're gonna pay for what you did to ginger.
-我对金杰做的就是打她。
- What I did to ginger is knock her around.
那么,婊子?
So what, bitch?
浪费时间…——该死的王八蛋。
Mess around... - Fucking asshole.
她死了，你这个蠢货!
She's dead, you dumb fuck!
-她死了，对吧?
- She's dead, huh?
-他们陷害我?
- They set me up, huh?
没人会陷害我，明白吗?
Nobody sets me up, you understand?
没有人!
Nobody!
来吧,开枪!
Come on, shoot!
来吧,警察。
Come on, cop.
Shoou不!
Shoou No!
来，杀了我，来吧。
Come on, kill me, come on.
门德斯，科瓦尔斯基，你们在哪?
Mendez, Kowalski, where are you guys?
-她死了，混蛋。
- She's dead, fuckhead.
你理解我吗?
You understand me?
死了,死了!
Dead, dead!
来吧,开枪!
Come on, shoot!
加油，加油!
Come on, come on!
你理解我!
You understand me!
死了!
Dead!
你他妈的猪!
You fucking pig!
我希望他们把你炸了!
I hope they fucking fry you!
——你死。
- You're dead.
你死了。
You're dead.
听到我的话，你就死定了。
You hear me, you're dead.
你死了,婊子!
You're dead, bitch!
你死了!
You're dead!
-来吧，你这个卑鄙小人。
- Come on, now, dirt bag.
来吧，废物。
Come on, dirt bag.
快，快，快!
Come on, come on, come on!
来吧,卑鄙的人。
Come on, scumbag.
让你的移动。
Make your move.
使我的一天。
Make my day.
两个热狗3.58美元。
$3.58 for two hot dogs.
有你的。
There's yours.
-你们看到了吗，那个小姜得到了一个体面的葬礼?
- You guys see that ginger gets a decent burial?
我是说，我一准备好就给你寄点钱。
I mean, I'll send some money as soon as I get set up.
-你不用担心这个。
- You don't worry about that.
县里会处理的。
The county is gonna take care of that.
-你结婚了吗?
- Are you married?
——没有。
- No.
从来没有结婚。
Never been married.
离过几次婚。
Have been divorced a few times.
-是啊，谁没有呢?
- Right, who hasn't, huh?
谁他妈会想嫁给一个警察?
Who'd wanna marry a fucking cop anyway?
-嘿，别这样。
- Hey, come on.
我们晚餐时聊得很愉快。
We make very good dinner conversation.
嗨，亲爱的，今天过得怎么样?
Hi, dear, how was your day today?
你懂的，还是老样子。
Oh, you know, the same old bull shit.
我抓到一个皮条客把他女朋友绑在床上然后往她身上倒打火机油，把她点着了。
I busted a pimp for tying his girlfriend up to a bed and then pouring lighter fluid all over and setting her on fire.
-我环游了世界两次。
- I went around the world twice.
——嗯。
- Hmm.
还有个13岁的妓女因为在日落大道掩护别人的地盘被我抓了。
Then there was the 13-year-old hooker I nailed for covering some guy's joint on sunset boulevard.
两个死了的瘾君子。
Two dead junkies.
一个16岁，一个14岁。
One is 16, the other one's 14.
-我打了几个怪胎。
- Well, I spanked a couple of freaks.
-又一个在缉捕队逍遥自在的日子。
- Just another happy-go-lucky day on the vice squad.
-我们住同一个厕所，沃尔什。
- We both live in the same toilet, Walsh.
谢谢你的热狗。
Thanks for the hot dog.
-嗨。
- Hey.
我送你回家吧。
Let me give you a ride home.
我今天早上睡了个美容觉。
- Well, I got my beauty sleep this morning.
别忘了，我可是个打工妹。
I'm a working girl in case you forgot.
-你今晚要去上班吗?
- You're gonna go to work tonight?
-我需要面包
- Well, I need the bread.
我不能在另一个城市免费安家。
I can't get set up in another town for free.
-嘿，嘿。
- Well, hey, hey.
等一下。
Wait a minute.
我给你一笔贷款。
I'm giving you a loan here.
-沃尔什，你真让人惊喜。
- Walsh, you are full of surprises.
你一个月挣的钱还不够我借钱给我。
You don't make enough in a month to loan me what I need.
-是啊，也许你能借我20块
- Yeah, well, maybe you could lend me a 20.
她很漂亮。
She's pretty.
-是的，她是。
- Yeah, she was.
——再见。
- Ciao.
保持干净，沃尔什。
Keep it clean, Walsh.
-往好的方面想，混蛋。
- Look at the bright side, asshole.
你有20年的时间来学习如何和自己玩。
You got 20 years to learn how to play with yourself.
——我很抱歉。
- I'm sorry.
-我朋友说得对，屁屁。
- My friend is right, butt breath.
你不再需要女人了。
You don't need women anymore.
也许是几张自慰的照片。
A few jerk-off pictures maybe.
-门德斯，凭他的才华，他可以给小弟拉皮条。
- Hey, Mendez, with his talent, he could pimp the bunboys.
-哦，啦啦。
- Ooh, la la.
别挡我的路!
Get out of my way!
-沃尔什会杀了我们的
- Walsh is gonna kill us.
我能理解你为什么不高兴。
I can understand why you're upset.
-你很幸运，科瓦尔斯基
- You're a lucky man, Kowalski.
你很幸运，那撬棍踢的是你的脸，而不是我因为我做得会好得多。
You're very lucky that ramrod kicked your face in and not me because I would have done a much better job of it.
——汤姆?
- Tom?
汤姆，别紧张，伙计。
Tom, take it easy, man.
不要着急。
Take it easy.
-你说他失控了
- You said he's out of control.
好吧，大家都知道这两名警官丢了子弹杆。
Okay, everybody knows that these two officers lost ramrod.
现在，我们该怎么做呢?
Now, what are we gonna do about that, huh?
嗯?
Huh?
外面有两个人在街上。
We got two people out there on the street.
底线是这样的。
Bottom line is this.
除非我们抓住其中一个，否则这女孩就死定了。
That unless we pick one of them up, we got a dead girl on our hands.
明白了吗?
Is that clear?
我是说，这很简单，不是吗?
I mean, it's very simple, isn't it?
我们发现他们。
We find them.
不是一个就是另一个。
One or the other.
现在，让我们上街吧。
Now, let's hit the streets.
如果他动了，你们就逮捕他。
You apprehend the bastard if he moves.
如果他敢眨眼或者摸他的屁股，你就干掉他。
If he so much as blinks or scratches his ass, you waste him.
你明白我的意思吗?
You got that?
我要的是他，不是你。
I want him out of commission, not you.
-拜托，拜托。
- Oh, please, please.
-放松，放松，放松。
- Easy, easy, easy.
-请帮帮我。——没关系。
- Please help me. - It's okay.
我马上找人来帮忙。
I'll get somebody here to help in a minute.
里奇，马上派人把这女孩送去医院。
Rich, you get a unit to transport this girl to a hospital right away.
好的，警官，马上。
Okay, sergeant, right away.
你这次又惹上了什么麻烦?
What kind of shit you got yourself into this time, huh?
-怎么，你腹泻了，是吗?
- What, you got diarrhea of the mouth, huh?
快点，罗斯科，快点。
Come on, Roscoe, move it.
挪开你的黑屁股，把我弄出去，好吗?
Move your black ass and get me out of this thing, will you?
-我告诉你，混蛋。
- Let me tell you something, motherfucker.
别跟我说这种屁话，听到了吗?
You don't talk that crappy shit to me, you hear?
你的手还被铐着。
Not with your hands cuffed.
因为我要烧了你的屁股。
'Cause I'll set your ass on fire.
你听到了吗?
Do you hear me?
——我很抱歉。
- I'm sorry.
真的,罗斯科。
Really, Roscoe.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
-抱歉，我的屁股。
- Sorry, my ass.
不是那个。
And not that one.
蓝色的福特。
The blue Ford.
500可不能让你得到黄金国。
我赊账做得够多了。
I done done enough on credit.
有你,男孩?
Have you, boy?
罗斯科，我告诉你。
Roscoe, I'll tell you what.
——什么?
- What?
你给艾迪打电话，告诉他我在路上了。
You call fast Eddie and you tell him I'm on my way.
-给我一角钱。
- Give me a dime.
-用我的信用卡。
- Put it on my credit card.
我很感激。
I appreciate it.
——这是50。
- Here's 50.
- 00 h 50 !
- 00h, 50!
你说的是25岁，亲爱的。
Well, you said 25, sweetheart.
额外的费用是什么?
What's the extra for?
你不想要直男性爱吗?
Don't you want straight sex?
——没有。
- No.
不,我要……
No, I want...
-你想要什么?
- Hmmm, what do you want?
-我想吸你的脚趾。
- I want to suck your toes.
-好吧，我去洗漱。
- Ooh, okay, I'll go wash up.
-哦,不。
- Oh, no.
不，没必要。
No, that won't be necessary.
——嗯。
- Hmm.
在我看来，你一直很淘气。
It seems to me that you have been very naughty.
——是的。
- Yes.
我是个很坏的男孩。
I've been a pretty bad boy.
——嗯。
- Mm-hmm.
既然你付了额外的钱，我觉得你应该被好好打一顿。
Well, since you paid extra, I think you deserve a good spanking.
-你好吗，艾迪?
- How're you doing, Eddie?
你觉得这样行吗?
Think this will do?
-真漂亮。
- Oh, that's beautiful.
这样就可以了。
That'll do just fine.
-这是你剩下的东西。
- Here's the rest of your stuff.
嘿,埃迪?
Hey, Eddie?
——哟。
- Yo.
-你到底想给我什么?
- What kind of shit are you trying to hand me?
我要自动手枪，明白吗?
I want an automatic, you understand?
自动的。
Automatic.
我现在就要，在我重新装饰你漂亮的小脑袋之前。
And I want it right now, before I redecorate that pretty little head of yours.
现在的行动。
Now move.
——推弹杆。
- Ramrod.
你坏。
You bad.
只要你按他说的做。
All you got to do his ask.
但是自动驾驶很贵。
But automatics are expensive.
-但你别担心，好吗?
- But don't you worry, all right?
没有汗水。
No sweat.
我的人会带着一袋纯白的亚洲人在你能跳出皮衣打你自己之前过来。
My man will be here with a bag of pure white Asian before you can jump out of your leathers and spank yourself.
听着，还有一件事。
Listen, one other thing.
你认识一个叫公主的贱人吗?
You know a bitch named Princess?
-是啊，但自从开了这个俱乐部我就没见过她。
- Yeah, but I ain't seen her since I opened this club.
-谁是她的皮条客?
- Well, who's her pimp?
-她没有皮条客
- She ain't got no pimp.
她是非法。
She's outlaw.
不,不。
No, no.
她刚来洛杉矶的时候有个皮条客。
She had a pimp when she first came to la.
-他是谁?
- Who was he?
他是谁?
Who was he?
来吧,埃迪。
Come on, Eddie.
-那个该死的皮条客多尔西
- That fucking sugar pimp, dorsey.
-多西?
- Dorsey?
他住在哪儿?
Where's he living?
-嘿，谁知道呢。
- Hey, who fucking knows.
-有人知道了，艾迪。
- Somebody knows, Eddie.
有人知道。
Somebody knows.
-查理·克里斯安德拉会知道的
- Hey, Charlie chrisandra would know.
——Chrisandra ?
- Chrisandra?
是的。
Yeah.
-你给他打个电话，好吗?
- Let's say you give him a call, all right?
-朋友帮什么忙都不为过。
- Oh, no favor is too big for a friend.
——打电话给他。
- Call him.
把你的手拿开
Get your hands off me.
阻止它。
Stop it.
把你的手拿开
Get your hands off of me.
放弃它。
Quit it.
去你妈的。
- Fuck you.
-天啊，你疯了
- God, you're crazy.
——耶稣,男人!
- Jesus, man!
今晚蝙蝠外出了。
The bats are out tonight.
我是说，妓女，同性恋，皮条客和皮条客。
I mean, whores, faggots, pimps and hustlers.
瘾君子，变装皇后和怪胎，伙计。
Junkies, drag queens and freaks, man.
这个城市很糟糕。
This city sucks.
警官，你在这片土地上工作了，大概13年吧?
Sergeant, you've been working this soil for, what, for 13 years?
你是怎么做到的?
How do you hack it?
-这是我给自己定的规矩。
- Well, this little rule I keep for myself.
爱德华兹，每周有两天我不用担心。
Edwards, there's two days out of every week I don't worry about.
昨天和明天。
Yesterday and tomorrow.
现在她他妈的在哪里?
Now where the fuck is she?
-谢谢你的治疗，医生。
- Thanks for the treatment, doc.
别把我的钱都花在同一个地方?
And don't go spending my money all in the same place, huh?
——别担心。
- Don't worry.
-嘿，等你在圣地亚哥安顿好了，告诉我你在哪，因为你绝对值得一趟。
- Hey, when you get settled in San Diego, you let me know where you're at, because, you're sure worth the trip.
再见,蒂姆。
Bye, Tim.
-嘿，宝贝。
- Hey, sugar baby.
我晚点再找你，好吗?
I'll catch you later, okay?
-我的主力，丝滑。
- My main man, silky.
我想和你谈谈，所以要注意听。
I want to talk to you so pay attention.
看那些照片。
Look at those photographs.
-从我面前消失，妈妈
- Get out of my face, mama.
你没有权利依靠我。
You ain't got no right to be leaning on me.
你怎么了?
What's wrong with you?
-不，是你出了什么问题
- No, it's what's going to be wrong with you.
-你什么意思，我有什么问题?
- What do you mean what's going to be wrong with me?
——嘿,嘿!
- Hey, hey!
-眨眼吧，混蛋，你就死在黑暗里。
- Blink your eyes, motherfuckers, and you die in the dark.
-你不是黑人，女人。
- You ain't black, woman.
你大便颜色的。
You shit colored.
没问题，杰克。
You got it, Jack.
-现在，你觉得你可以表现得像个绅士，回答这位女士的问题吗?
- Now, you think you can act like a gentleman and answer the lady's questions?
还是让我重新排列你的脸?
Or do I re-arrange your face?
——好吧,男人。
- Okay, man.
冷静点，伙计。
Just cool it, man.
只是很酷。
Just cool it.
-好吧，丝滑，我们再试一次。
- Okay, silky, let's try it again.
看那张照片。
Look at that photograph.
-我认识这个变态白鬼
- Yeah, I know this psycho honky.
他之前在这里。
He was in here earlier.
从那以后我就没见过他。
I ain't seen him since.
-我们在哪能找到他?
- Where can we find him?
-这对我有什么好处?
- What's in it for me?
-安心，兄弟。
- Peace of mind, brother.
-试试罗斯科在贝伦多的车库。
- Well, try Roscoe's garage over in berendo.
-非常感谢您的合作，先生。
- Thank you very much for your cooperation, sir.
-我喜欢在家看电视。
- I like to be home watching television.
对我来说，街上的压力太大了。
There's just too much heat on the street for me.
我的帽子在哪里?
Where's my hat?
-给你。
- Here it is.
给我。
Give me that.
那些警察太过分了。
Those cops was out of line.
幸运的是，我没发脾气。
Lucky for them punks, I kept my temper.
3.50美元,女士。
$3.50, ma'am.
——保持它。
- Keep it.
嘿!
Hey!
——嘿,迪克西。
- Hey, Dixie.
你好吗?
How are you doing?
你看起来很好。
You look great.
——公主。
- Princess.
——嗨,可可。
- Hi, coco.
-你最近去哪儿了?
- Where have you been lately?
好久没见到你了。
Haven't seen you in a while.
-我感冒了
- I had the flu.
医生说我得卧床休息几天。
The doctor said I had to stay out of bed for a few days.
-我今晚被抓了。
- I got busted tonight.
你在开玩笑吧!-哦,不。
- You're kidding! - Oh, no.
-我的皮条客不到一个小时就交了保释金
- It took my pimp less than an hour to post bond.
哦,这是太快了。
Ooh, that's fast.
这是太快了。
That is fast.
-他知道我坐在监狱里是赚不到钱的。
- Well, he knows my pussy can make no money sitting in the slammer.
-今晚过得好吗?
- You having a good night?
-只有希腊人和怪胎。
- Nothing but Greeks and freaks.
我告诉你没人想要异性恋性爱了。
I tell you nobody wants straight sex anymore.
-我很幸运。
- I got lucky.
我今晚要和一个被吊死的男人约会。
I have a date tonight with guy who was hung like a horse.
我是说，太大了，他必须在分部里硬起来。
I mean, so big, he had to get it hard in sections.
-我有个值班的。
- I had a clock watcher.
他以为我按分钟收费。
He thought I was charging him by the minute.
-姑娘，这些怪人，他们都一样。
- Girl, these kinda freaks, they're all alike.
他们想以同样的价格卖两次。
They wanna pop twice for the same price.
-敬怪胎。
- Here's to freaks.
——是的,狂。
- Yeah, freaks.
——嘿,漂亮。
- Hey, beautiful.
你想去天堂旅行吗。
How'd you like a trip to paradise.
-看情况吧。
- Now, that depends.
你是朋友还是敌人?
You a friend or foe?
-亲爱的，你眼前的是一个饥渴的与会者。
- Sweetheart, you're looking at a horny conventioneer.
听他的话。
Listen to him.
-看到这张脸了吗?
- See this face?
我见过的驴比牛仔的马鞍还多。
Seen more ass than a cowboy's saddle.
你能搞定我吗?
Think you can handle me?
-先生，我能搞定整个大会。
- Mister, I can handle the whole god damn convention.
她能应付两种惯例。
She can handle two conventions.
-再见，公主。
- See you later, Princess.
再见。
See you later.
我会简短明了的。
I'll keep it short and sweet.
-我知道你会的
- Whoo, I know you will.
——再见,公主。再见,宝贝。
- Bye, Princess. - Bye, sweetheart.
玩得开心。
Have fun.
就是这个晚上我一定会来的，我来了。
J this is the night j j for sure j I'm coming, I'm coming.
我什么都有
J I have everything j
现在我知道你认识一个叫公主的贱人。
Now I understand that you know a bitch named Princess.
我说的对吗，孩子?
Am I right, boy?
-我还没见过她呢
- Man, I haven't seen her.
拜托，你弄疼我了。
Oh, please, man, you're hurting me.
我伤害你。
I'm hurting you.
孩子，她住在哪里?
Where does she live, boy?
-她从没告诉过我
- She never told me.
-她常去哪里?
- Where does she hang out?
嗯,嗯?
Huh, huh?
酒吧、旅馆。
Bars, motels.
回答我。
Answer me.
——好莱坞,好莱坞。
- Hollywood, Hollywood.
——好莱坞吗?
- Hollywood?
好莱坞在哪里?
Where in Hollywood?
——日落。
- Sunset.
——在那里,在哪里?
- Where, where?
在哪里?
Where?
-黄金旅馆，伙计。
- The golden motel, man.
——嘘。
- Shh.
嘘,嘘。
Shh, shh.
你知道你们这些糖皮条客有什么问题吗?
You know what the problem is that you sugar pimps have?
你不知道怎么对付你的婊子。
You don't know how to handle your bitches.
为什么?
Why?
因为我觉得你没种，小子。
'Cause I don't think you got any balls, boy.
嘿,婊子。
- Hey, bitch.
我他妈付钱给你干什么?
What the fuck am I paying you for?
来吧。
Come on.
来，动起来。
Come on move it.
滚远点，贱人。
Move your ass, bitch.
-你他妈在干什么?
- What the fuck are you doing?
你是个讨厌的混蛋。
You're a lousy piece of ass.
我要拿回我的钱。
I'm taking my money back.
把包给我，你这该死的…
Give my purse, you fucking...
——耶稣。
- Jesus.
你做了什么?
What did you do?
搞了整个足球队?
Fucked the whole football team?
你该庆幸我没有因为你浪费我的时间而向你收费。
You know, you're lucky I'm not charging you for wasting my time.
-去吧，混蛋。
- Go ahead, motherfucker.
有个黑鬼皮条客很卑鄙，等他把你干掉，你会祈祷自己死掉。
I got a nigger pimp so mean, when he gets through with you, you'll pray you'll die.
混蛋。
Asshole.
你会祈祷自己死掉的，你这个该死的混蛋。
You'll pray you'll die, you lousy fucking asshole.
-他一点也不想成为谋杀案的从犯。
- He's not at all anxious to be an accessory to murder.
是吗，罗斯科，宝贝?
Are you, Roscoe, baby?
正确的。
Right.
拉姆罗德开着一辆1979年的福特四轮马车，刚刚重新漆成了蓝色。
Ramrod's driving a 1979 Ford brougham, just repainted blue.
再派一队人去艾迪酒吧。
Also get a team over to fast Eddie's bar.
拉姆罗德去那里拿了把枪。
Ramrod went there to get a gun.
你很合作，罗斯科。
You're so cooperative, Roscoe.
不错,罗斯科。
Nice, Roscoe.
克鲁克香克太太，帮我拿些干净的床单来，好吗?
- Mrs. Cruikshank, do me a favor and get me some clean sheets, will ya?
-公主殿下以为这是他妈的广场酒店。
- Her royal highness thinks this is the fucking Plaza hotel.
这是谁的动作，王?
Who's move is it, wong?
-我相信是我的，克鲁克香克夫人。
- I believe it is mine, Mrs. Cruikshank.
来,打我。
Come, beat me.
6v3，我们刚刚覆盖了好莱坞圆形区域。
Six Victor three, we just covered the Hollywood bowl area.
我们一无所获。
We drew a blank.
大便。
Shit.
6victor 7，你有什么发现吗?
Six Victor seven, have you got anything?
6号，维克多，7号，没有。
Six Victor seven, negative.
我们在好莱坞和卡亨加街交界处。
We're at Hollywood and cahuenga.
-公主，我们今晚不受欢迎吗?
- Well, Princess, ain't we the popular one tonight.
-你在说什么?
- What are you talking about?
-有人在停车场等你。
- Someone's waiting for you in the parking lot.
我点名要找你。
Asked for you by name.
25美元。
原谅我。
Pardon me.
你想念公主吗?
Are you miss Princess?
-那得看情况。
- Well, that depends.
-我跟克鲁克香克夫人说过，你是一个叫可可的小姐介绍给我的。
- As I told madam cruikshank, you were referred to me by a certain miss coco.
我的雇主想利用你的服务。
My employer would like to avail himself of your services.
-他有什么想法?
- Now what does he have in mind?
-你得和他商量一下。
- You'll have to discuss that with him.
——你好,沃尔什。
- Hello, Walsh.
我想我最好让你知道这件事。
I thought I better let you in on this one.
你有什么发现，布鲁克斯?
What have you got, Brooks?
-有个小丑刚割了一个叫多尔西的皮条客的性腺。
- Some joker just cut the gonads off a sugar pimp named dorsey.
可能是你的儿子。
Could have been your boy.
多尔西说他在找一个叫公主的小妓女。
Dorsey said he was looking for a little hooker named Princess.
他告诉拉姆罗德去哪里找她了吗?
Did he tell ramrod where to find her?
是的，他说是黄金旅馆。
Yeah, he said the golden motel.
——哦,大便。
- Oh, shit.
那是长街的另一端。
That's the other end of the strip.
六个维克多小队，疑犯正前往黄金汽车旅馆，日落大道和卡亨加大道。
All six Victor units, suspect heading for golden motel, sunset and cahuenga.
公主在哪里?
Where's Princess?
-冷静点，你个蠢货。
- Cool it, you big palooka.
你会害死我们的。
You're gonna get us killed.
-我们要对付的是一个能把我们炸飞的变态混蛋。
- We're coming up against a psycho asshole who can blow us away, man.
你在担心一个小车祸。
You're worried about a fucking little Fender bender.
-谁会担心一个小车祸?
- Who's worried about a fucking Fender bender?
你不怕吗?
Doesn't anything scare you?
——是的,男人。
- Yeah, man.
所有的时间。
All the time.
你以为我每晚为什么会做那些该死的噩梦?
Why do you think I have those god damn nightmares every night?
-那些都是梦。
- Those are just dreams.
平淡，每一天，平凡的梦想。
Plain, every day, ordinary dreams.
小心!
Watch it!
这是一场噩梦。
This is a nightmare.
把它,科瓦尔斯基。
Take it, Kowalski.
这里到底发生了什么?
What in the hell happened here?
-你们猪总是一样的。
- You pigs are always alike.
一天后，差一美元。
A day later, a dollar short.
这是事实。
And that's the truth.
-克利弗先生在这里跳踢踏舞吗?
- Did Mr. Cleaver tap-dance through here?
-给我滚出去。
- Get the hell out of here.
——听着,女士。
- Listen, lady.
就是这个人吗?
Is this the guy?
-给我滚出去。
- Get the hell out of here.
-她是我朋友。
- She's my friend.
你最好离克鲁克香克夫人远点。
You better leave madam cruikshank alone.
-把这个装饰品从我脸上拿开。
- Get this ornamental out of my face.
嘿，伙计，不是鼻子。
Hey, man, not the nose.
-好了，李小龙，够了。
- Okay, Bruce Lee, enough of that shit.
-我叫王，不是李。
- My name is wong, not Lee.
——好吧,黄。
- Okay, wong.
——好吧!
- Okay!
你，狗娘养的。
You, son of a bitch.
不是鼻子。
Not the nose.
——冻结,先生。
- Freeze, mister.
生硬的在哪里?
Where's ramrod?
-我们错过他了，汤姆。
- We missed him, Tom.
多好的谋生手段啊。
What a way to make a living.
——我也有同感。
- I'll say.
我想我要杀了这个混蛋。
I think I'll shoot the bastard.
-在六点钟的新闻上不会好看的。
- Wouldn't look good on the six o'clock news.
克鲁克山克，你跟拉姆罗德说了什么?
Okay, cruikshank, what did you tell ramrod?
-我什么都没告诉他
- I didn't tell him nothing.
——废话。
- Bullshit.
如果你什么都不告诉他，你现在就不会活着了。
If you didn't tell him anything, you wouldn't be alive right now.
-我什么都没告诉他
- I didn't tell him nothing.
嗨,迪克西。
Hey, Dixie.
到这里来。
Come on over here.
加油，加油，宝贝。
Come on, come on, baby.
我只想和你谈谈。
All I wanna do is talk to you.
你好吗，迪克西?
How you doing, Dixie?
听着，我的皮条客看到我和你说话，他会把我打得屁滚尿流的。
- Listen, ramrod, my pimp sees me talking to you, he'll beat the shit out of me.
-嘘，放松点，贱人。
- Shh, just relax, bitch.
现在你能告诉我什么是大型凯迪拉克豪华轿车。
Now what can you tell me about a big, Cadillac limousine.
-那是coco的演出。
- Oh, that's coco's gig.
-那是coco的演出，对吧?
- That's coco's gig, huh?
谁他妈的是可可，贱人?
Who the fuck is coco, bitch?
-只是其中一个女孩。
- Just one of the girls.
-穿粉红色衣服的那个，在那个角落。
- The one in the pink, at the corner there.
请,请。
Please, please.
——请,死板的人。——嘘。
- Please, ramrod. - Shh.
你好。
Hello.
-你好，美女。
- Well, hello, beautiful.
-你是警察吗?
- Are you a cop?
-我是警察吗?
-Am I a cop?
我他妈像什么猪吗?
What do I look like some kind of fucking pig?
——也许。
- Maybe.
你在找对象吗?
You looking for a date?
-是啊，是啊，我在找对象。
- Yeah, yeah, I'm looking for a date.
你为什么不靠近一点。
Why don't you come here a little closer.
我听说你很厉害。
I hear you're good.
你真的很棒吗?
Are you real good?
-嗯，好吧，好吧，我没有抱怨。
- Hmm, well, well, I had no complaints.
-那辆凯迪拉克把公主带去哪了?
- Where did that Cadillac take the Princess?
我说，它把她带到哪里去了?
I said, where did it take her?
在哪里?
Where?
-可可!
- Coco!
-嘿，这是…——嘘。
- Hey, what the... - Shh.
记住，一个字也不要说。
Remember, not a word.
你同意了。
You agreed.
-恶心的老混蛋。
- Sick old fuck head.
你吓死我了。
You scared the shit out of me.
-你毁了它，荡妇。
- You ruined it, slut.
罗伯茨告诉过你不要说话。
Roberts told you not to talk.
你毁了它。
You ruined it.
-我可能会死于心脏病。
- I could have died of a fucking heart attack.
-罗伯茨。
- Roberts.
她说。
She talked.
-我让她不要的，先生
- I instructed her not to, sir.
-但她做到了。
- But she did.
把那个荡妇带出去。
Get that slut out of here.
——是的,先生。
- Yes, sir.
请跟我来。
Please, come with me.
-就该去疯人院，你个狗娘养的。
- Belong in a fucking loony bin, you son of a bitch.
天啊，你怎么不警告我?
Jesus Christ, why didn't you warn me?
-我有指示。
- I have my instructions.
你最好去换衣服。
You better go change.
-那个老家伙50年前就该死了。
- That old shit should have died 50 years ago.
-有辆出租车在等你，公主小姐。
- There's a taxi waiting for you, miss Princess.
-我不会付钱的
- I'm not paying for it.
-已经处理好了
- It's been taken care of.
你每天晚上都工作吗?
Do you work every night?
-算了，我这周已经受够惊吓了。
- Forget it, I've already had my scare for the week.
-不，你不明白
- No, you don't understand.
明天晚上我休息。
Tomorrow night's my night off.
你会工作吗?
Will you be working?
-我会在教堂里请求上帝原谅那个老混蛋。
- I'll be in church asking god to forgive that old fuck.
打个电话，搭档，告诉他我们找到可可了。
Get on the horn, partner, and tell him we found coco.
女,东方,所在地。
Female, oriental, located.
友好的建议。
Advised as friendly.
可能在第七街和罗斯莫尔街交口。
Possibly at 7th and Rossmore.
——罗杰,中央。
- Roger, central.
这是6个维克多10对所有6个维克多单位。
This is six Victor 10 to all six Victor units.
我们知道公主的位置了。
We have a location on Princess.
在第七街和罗斯莫尔街交汇处汇合。
Converge at 7th and Rossmore.
重复一遍，在第七大道和罗斯莫尔路口汇合。
I repeat, converge at 7th and Rossmore.
用锤子敲吧，爱德华兹。
Put the hammer to it, Edwards.
——嗨,妈妈。
- Hi, ma.
你好,是我。
Hi, it's me.
抱歉这么晚打给你，但我得想想丽莎的事。
I'm sorry I'm calling so late, but, oh, I just got to thinking about Lisa.
我才不管他做了什么。
I don't give a damn what he did.
看看他对可可做了什么。
Look what he did to coco.
我没办法。
I couldn't help it.
他用刀指着我的脸。
He had a knife to my face.
-我才不在乎呢
- I don't give a damn.
看看他对可可做了什么。
Look what he did to coco.
听着，我不想和你说话。
Listen, I don't want to talk to you.
我不管有什么问题。
I don't care what the problem was.
你什么都不该告诉他。
You shouldn't have told him anything.
公主!
There's Princess!
-哦，我希望你不要哭。
- Oh, I wish you wouldn't cry.
-我想我们最好告诉她拉姆罗德的事。
- I think we better tell her about ramrod.
哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my god!
有什么事吗?
What's the matter?
-他来了。
- There he is.
公主!
Princess!
嘿,女士!
Hey, lady!
你知道你在干什么吗?
What do you think you're doing?
你好,公主。
Hello, Princess.
我得到了你。
I got you.
-快报警。
- Somebody call the cops.
-她几分钟前刚走。
- And she left just a few minutes ago.
-但你没听到她告诉司机她要去哪里吗?
- But you didn't hear her tell the driver where she wanted to go?
-我以为她…-沃尔什，他抓住她了。
- I thought she... - Walsh, he's got her.
他在一辆白色小货车里。
He's in a white pickup truck.
最后一次看到他是在范内斯，在圣莫尼卡往南走。
He was last seen on Van ness, heading south on Santa Monica.
-我发布了一个绑架广播。
- I put out a kidnapping broadcast.
- - - - - -来吧。
- Come on.
嘿，我们要去哪儿?
Hey, where are we going?
范内斯街和圣莫尼卡街交叉口。
South on Van ness and Santa Monica.
好了，开始。
Okay, here we go.
搬出去。
Move out.
封锁小巷。
Cover the side streets.
好的,我们走吧。
Okay, let's go.
你们黑人和白人掩护布朗森。
You black and whites cover Bronson.
科瓦尔斯基，你负责微科。
Kowalski, you take pico.
我们去范内斯。
We'll take Van ness.
-是的，是的，是的。
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
总部，有皮卡的消息吗?
Central, any word of pickup truck?
还没有，6号维克多10号。
Nothing yet, six Victor 10.
我们让每个人都在努力。
We have everyone working on it.
你打算进行监视吗?
Do you plan on running surveillance?
-是的，我们得先找到他。
- Affirmative, we have to find him first.
从范内斯到佛蒙特。
Pico from Van ness to Vermont.
没有迹象表明。
No sign.
继续往东走。
Continue east on pico.
6v7，你在哪里?
Six Victor seven, what is your location?
-我们往北走，往西走，华盛顿以南。
- We're heading north on western, south of Washington.
这里是一号玛丽，m32呼叫六号维克多10。
This is one Mary, m32 to six Victor 10.
我们发现可疑车辆在贝弗利街和林登街交叉口向东行驶。
We have spotted suspect vehicle heading east on Beverly and linden.
我们在下面。
We are following.
-收到，一号二号。
- Roger, one Mary X-ray two.
车辆不能，重复，在任何情况下都不能被逮捕。
Vehicle is not, repeat is not under any circumstances to be apprehended.
我们会设立一个监测点，保持动态监控。
We will establish a point and maintain a moving surveillance.
嫌犯车辆正往牛津街南行。
Suspect vehicle is now heading south on Oxford.
6victor 7号，我们离他们最近，我们会抓到他们的。
Six Victor seven, we are closest, we'll pick 'em up.
-好吧，你说对了。
- Okay, you got the point.
听着，6号维克多7号和所有其他单位。
Listen, six Victor seven and all other units.
不要靠近推杆。
Do not close in on ramrod.
如果他看到我们，他会杀了公主的。
If he sees us, he'll kill Princess.
他着陆后我们会接近的。
We'll close in when he lands.
-拉姆罗德在奥林匹克公路上向东行驶，行驶不稳定。
- Ramrod heading east on olympic, driving erratically.
-我们有后门，在我们后面大约半英里处。
- We got the back door, about a half a mile behind.
保持冷静，我们可不想烫伤他。
Now keep it cool, we don't want to burn him.
——罗杰。
- Roger.
6号，维克多3号，你在哪里?
Six Victor three, where are you?
-我们与车辆平行，在pico上向东行驶。
- We are parallel to the vehicle, heading east on pico.
——婊子。
- Bitch.
-拉姆罗德现在在阿尔梅达街第四大道向东行驶。
- Ramrod now heading east on Almeida at 4th.
我想我们可能会被烧伤。
I think we might get burned.
我们开始剥了。
So we're peeling off.
-收到，6号，维克多7号。
- Roger, six Victor seven.
6号，维克多3号，负责，但别让人看见。
Six Victor three, take the point, but stay out of sight.
找到他了，他在阿尔梅达街，经过一街。
We've got him, he's on Almeida passing lst.
-你喜欢咬人吗?
- You like to bite?
-那混蛋正在过第六街大桥。
- The asshole's crossing the 6th street bridge.
落在后面。
Drop back.
不要他。
Don't crowd him.
——啊!
- Ah!
母狗!
Bitch!
——就是这样。
- That's it.
我们的鸽子着陆了。
Our pigeon has landed.
是一间仓库，在第七街和磨坊街的拐角处。
It's a warehouse, corner of 7th and mill street.
-所有六组维克多小队，行动。
- To all six Victor units, move in.
——罗杰。
- Roger.
-你看，公主，我对金儿做的事，跟我要对你做的事比起来，算不了什么。
- You see, Princess, what I did to ginger, it ain't nothing, compared to what I'm going to do to you.
别再踢我了，贱人。
No more kicking, bitch.
别再挠了，明白吗?
No more scratching, you understand me?
因为现在轮到我了。
'Cause now it's my turn.
该死的!
God damn it!
他们在哪儿?
Where are they?
-我想他们在五楼。
- I think they're up there in the fifth floor.
-我会找到你的，贱人。
- I'm going to find you, bitch.
你听到我吗?
You hear me?
我会找到你的。
I'm going to find you.
这是结束了。
It's over.
结束了。
Over.
我们在皮卡上发现了这个。
We found this in the pickup.
看起来他们在五楼。
Looks like they're on the fifth floor.
-有多少权限?
- How many accesses?
-这里有楼梯，防火梯在后面。
- Well, there is the stairs here and the fire escape's in the back.
-货运电梯被关闭了。
- The freight elevator's been shut off.
-爱德华兹和我走防火梯。
- Edwards and I will take the fire escape.
你和科瓦尔斯基走楼梯。
You and Kowalski take the stairs.
露易丝和克里斯支援他们，带上几套制服。
Louise and Chris back them up, take a couple of uniforms with you.
等我的信号。
Wait for my signal.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
消防通道。
Fire escape.
——爸爸。
- Pop.
哦,是的。
Oh, yes.
哦，是的，我喜欢。
Oh yes, I love it.
不!
No!
哦,是的,是的。
Oh, yeah, yeah.
——不!
- No!
——这是发薪日。
- It's payday.
-天啊，不。
- Oh, god, no.
不,请。
No, please.
请,不。
Please, no.
哦,不。
Oh, no.
请不要。
Don't, please.
准备好了吗?
Ready?
——我们准备好了。
- We're ready.
走了。
Go.
冻结!
Freeze!
这混蛋。
Hold it motherfucker.
婊子养的。
Son of a bitch.
我就在你后面。
I'm right behind you.
小心，靠窗的地方。
Watch it, by the window.
在屋顶上。
There on the roof.
-检查防火梯。
- Check fire escape.
该死的。
God damn it.
得到一辆救护车。
Get an ambulance.
马上军士。
Right away, sarge.
盖住防火梯。
Cover the fire escape.
-抓住他。
- Just get him.
-你好好照顾她
- You take care of her.
来吧,克里斯。
Come on, Chris.
——嘿,移动。
- Hey, move.
我说的举动。
I said move.
冻结。
Freeze.
-跳，你这个混蛋。
- Jump, you asshole.
6号，维克多10号，你在哪里?
Six Victor 10, where are you?
什么……
What...
13号呼叫中士，一号中心。
放轻松。
Just take it easy.
会没事的，好吗?
It's gonna be all right, okay?
好吧。
Okay.
保持担架水平。
Keep the stretcher level.
小心些而已。
Be careful.
提前打电话提醒他们。
Phone ahead and alert them.
-他能挺过来吗?
- Is he gonna make it?
-如果他不，我就杀了这个狗娘养的。
- If he doesn't, I'll kill the son of a bitch.
-我想这是你的。
- I think this belongs to you.
-看在上帝的份上，沃尔什
- For Christ's sake, Walsh.
上面全是血。
It has blood all over it.
-我再给你拿一杯。
- Well, I'll get you another one.
-我不知道你为什么要这么做。
- I don't know why you do it.
你永远改变不了街道，沃尔什。
You're never gonna change the streets, Walsh.
渐入黑色渐入街道生机勃勃渐入大城市的怪物渐入睁眼渐入喧嚣，渐入肌肉渐入铬和钢铁渐入你得到了我想要的渐入让我们做笔交易渐入
J fade into black j j the streets come alive j j that big city monster j j just opened his eyes j j the hustle, the muscle j j the chrome and the steel j j you got what I want j j let's make a deal j
砰，砰，把他们打死j j谈论犯罪j j有人买了它j j在霓虹灯黏液j j是的，每个人都在霓虹灯黏液中溺水j j你看我是幸存者j
j bang bang, shoot 'em up j j talkin' 'bout crime j j somebody just bought it j j in the neon slime j j yeah, everybody's drownin' in the neon slime j j you see I'm the survivor j
我知道这是什么感觉j j成为夜晚的一部分一切都是真实的j j音乐，暴力，性爱，甜蜜的气味j j我是一个冰冷的信徒
j and I know how it feels j j to be part of the night j j where everything is real j j the music, the violence j j the sex, the sweet smell j j I'm a stone-cold believer j
J在地狱的乐趣J J砰砰，射他们J J感觉很好J J在河中受洗J J在霓虹灯黏液J
j in the pleasures of hell j j bang bang, shoot 'em up j j feelin' just fine j j been baptized in the river j j of the neon slime j
是的，这是真的J这是你特别的梦想J比生活更大J这会让你想要尖叫J最新的愤怒J最新的热门J现在它来了J
j yes, it's real j j it's your special dream j j larger than life j j it's gonna make you wanna scream j j the latest rage j j and the latest hit j j now here it comes j
j我给你带来快乐j j也给你带来痛苦j j但我向你保证j j你再也不会是以前的j j来品尝我的蜂蜜j j尝我的酒j j来触摸我的灵魂j
j I bring you pleasure j j and I bring you pain j j but I promise you this j j you'll never be the same j j come taste my honey j j and taste my wine j j come touch my soul j
我在队伍的最后砰砰砰，把他们打死我谈论犯罪我在霓虹灯黏液的河里游泳街道上到处都是霓虹灯黏液
j at the end of the line j j bang bang, shoot 'em up j j talkin' 'bout crime j j swimmin' in the river of the neon slime j j the streets are flowin' with neon slime j
我在水上行走
J walkin' on the water j
霓虹灯黏液
J of neon slime j